Hello.
In this lecture, we're going to make it so that we can kill our boss.
If we open up the boss animation blueprint.
And in some free space, right click and go, jump and just call this jump node.
Die.
And just drive off here.
I look for animation state and just call this our boss die.
If we head inside here, right click and find the post die animation.
And just connect it into here and select it.
And just make sure to uncheck loop animation as we don't want this animation to loop.
We can then compile this and go over to our boss blueprint.
Now, if we attack our boss and it has helped less than or equal to zero, we'll tell the game that
our boss is dead.
So our drag in this is dead and set it and just make sure to check it and connect true into here.
When our boss is dead, we're going to stop its movement and or make it so it can't attack the player
character.
So if I go over to event tech, I'm going to delete this and instead I'm going to have a branch and
the condition is going to be is dead.
As long as this is false, then my boss will move.
If I go over to my boss attacking with the condition, we can't just drag up here and look for or boolean
and just drag in is dead.
So if my boss is damaged or dead, it's not going to attack our player character.
Okay.
After we do this, we're going to call a jump to Node.
So just copy us.
And with the jump name I called mine Di.
Then after a delay of, let's say.
2 seconds, we can destroy our boss.
So drag off it and look for destroyed actor and just go compile to make this easy for me.
I'm just going to give my boss three health.
So under variable, under default value.
I'm going to change this to be three and go compile and close this.
I'm just going to design my boss map a bit more.
So if we go to the item folder and just drag in a platform.
Or leave it to layer 20, because that's where all my boss and player character is.
And I place a platform here and a platform at the edge here.
In case the player wants to jump on them so they could play.
I should now be able to kill my boss.
So human health.
Okay, so my boss died, and then I played the Boss death animation, and then my boss was destroyed.
So maybe that was a bit easy.
So maybe I should adjust some of the settings of the boss.
But basically, our boss can now die in the game.
It would have more help, though, to be fair.